let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "It is an HTML tag at which a style will be applied. This could be any tag like < h1 > or < table > etc.",
        answer: "A. Selector",
        options: [
            "A. Selector",
            "B. Property",
            "C. Value",  
            "D. Style" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "It is a type of attribute of HTML tag where all the HTML attributes are converted into CSS properties.",
        answer: "B. Property",
        options: [
            "A. Selector",
            "B. Property", 
            "C. Value",
            "D. Tag"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "In the CSS style rule, It is assigned to properties.",
        answer: "C. Value",
        options: [
            "A. Selector‚Äù ", 
            "B. Property ", 
            "C. Value ", 
            "D. CSS style " 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "In the following CSS style rule, what does the type selectors do?",
        answer: "A. Applies color to all level 1 headings",
        options: [
            "A. Applies color to all level 1 headings",
            "B. Sets background color",
            "C. Defines a font style color",
            "D. None of the above"

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "When using descendant selectors, how is the style rule applied?",
        answer: "A. It will apply to element only when it lies inside the tag",
        options: [
            "A.  It will apply to element only when it lies inside the tag", 
            "B. The tag will only apply to the element", 
            "C. It will applies all of the tags outside the element", 
            "D. All of the above" 

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which selectors are defined for based on the class attributes of the elements?",
        answer: "C. Class selectors",
        options: [
            "A. Type selectors", 
            "B. Descendant selectors", 
            "C. Class Selectors", 
            "D. Universal selectors" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which selectors are defined for based on the id attributes of the elements?",
        answer: "B. ID selectors",
        options: [
            "A. Type selectors", 
            "B. ID selectors", 
            "C. Class selectors", 
            "D. Descendant selectors" 

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What type of CSS selector is described that is similar to descendants but has different functionality?",
        answer: "B. Child selectors",
        options: [
            "A. Sibling selectors",
            "B. Child selectors",
            "C. Universal selectors",
            "D. Attribute selectors"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What does the universal selector (*) do in the following CSS rule? ",
        answer: "D. Matches the name of any element type",
        options: [
            "A. Applies color to all level 1 headings",
            "B. Targets only 1 headings",
            "C. Selects elements of a specific type",
            "D. Matches the name of any element type"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which selectors does (ul em) have? ",
        answer: "A. Descendant selectors",
        options: [
            "A. Descendant selectors ", 
            "B. Universal selectors", 
            "C. Type selectors", 
            "D. Class selectors"            

        ]
    },
]